Name: Basanta Shrestha

Address: Khushibun, Nayabazar

Phone: 9869114675

Email: 13asanta.shrestha@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Diligent web developer with a Bachelor's qualification in Computer Science and information technology, and expecting to enhance my expert involvement in an IT organization specializing in web development. Armed with a profound awareness of other's expectations and having extremely significant levels of eagerness to give my 110% for any undertaking.

Core Qualifications:

• Languages: HTML, CSS, Python and JavaScript

• Frameworks: Bootstrap, Django

• Designing tools: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Lightroom

• Documentation: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint

Professional Qualifications:

- A certified Microsoft Office Specialist of the year 2015
- A working knowledge gained through the completion of Web Development Camp held by Microsoft Innovation Center Nepal
- Experience in project management and team leading environment

Experience:

• Web Designer (01/2018-06/2019)

Thakur International and Investment Pvt. Ltd.

Duties:

- establish the purpose of the website based upon its target audience
- identify the type of content the site will host
- give guidance on layout, colours and styles
- demonstrating designing skills with photoshop and illustrator
- managing a team and meeting the deadline of the project
- handling client by prioritizing their requirements
- Digital Marketing (06/2017-07/2018) DeliBird Apparel Line (Own Startup)
- Independent tutor (2013-2016)

Education:

- Bachelors of Science in Computer Science and Information Technology (B.Sc. CSIT) Prime College (2014-2018)
- Higher Secondary Course in Science Prime College (2012-2014)

Personal Projects:

- Online Car Rental System Application (09/2018-02/2019)
- Management Information System (05/2016-07/2016)

Skills:

- Excellent Communication Skill
- Proper Team Management Skill
- Analytical and Time Management Skill
- Up-to-date with the advancement in the industry
- Always focused in designing unique user experience and interface

Languages:

• English: Bilingual Proficiency

• Nepali: Native Proficiency

• Hindi: Professional Proficiency

• Japanese: Elementary Proficiency

Reference:

Mr. Shahadev Basnet

Branch Manager

Mega Bank Nepal Limited

9851201283